

114 Park Lane UB4 8AF · 07475924326 alitahir_@outlook.com

A second-year Computer Science undergraduate at University of Surrey with experience as a Computer Science Lab helper and significant customer service experience. Currently, in my placement year working as a IT Support Engineer at FootfallCam

EXPERIENCE

JULY 2019 - PRESENT

PASSENGER SERVICE AGENT, WILSON JAMES

Ensure a smooth, seamless passenger journey through the airport by assisting, welcoming and engaging with them to deliver legendary service

SEPTEMBER 2020 – PRESENT

PEER ASSISTED LEARNING SUPPORT, UNIVERSITY OF SURREY

Help students complete lab tasks by answering queries they have. Helped Year-One students undertaking the Web & Database Systems module in Semester One. Currently, helping Year-One students undertaking the Operating Systems module in Semester Two.

JULY 2021 - MARCH 2022

IT SUPPORT ENGINEER, FOOTFALLCAM

Delivered people counting solutions to clients. Helped troubleshoot and diagnose issues clients faced with software.

OCTOBER 2020 – MARCH 2021

TUTOR, HESTON LEARNING CENTRE

Tutor students of all ages (KS1 to A-Level) in Mathematics and Physics

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2019 – JUNE 2023

BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF SURREY

Currently finished my second year, averaged a first-class grade (90%) throughout the year, on course to achieving a first-class degree.

Relevant modules include Computer Logic, Foundations of Computing I & II, Programming Fundamentals, Web & Database Systems, Software Engineering, Operating Systems, Data Structure and Algorithms, Further Programming Paradigms, Information Retrieval, Advanced Algorithms, Web Applications Development, Artificial Intelligence, Computer Networking, Parallel Computing.

The course combines practical projects and theoretical study, developing technical and transferable skills in:

- Web Development Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, XML, jQuery and Ruby
- Programming Languages: Assembly Language, C, C++, Haskell, Python and Java

• Numerical computing Environments: MATLAB, R and SageMath

JUNE 2019

A LEVELS, ROSEDALE COLLEGE

- Mathematics A
- Physics A
- ICT B

JUNE 2016

GCSE, ROSEDALE COLLEGE

- Mathematics A*
- English Literature A
- Additional Science A
- R.E A
- Citizenship A
- Statistics A

- French B
- English Language B
- Core Science B
- ICT B
- History B

SKILLS

- SQL
- Java
- Web Design
- Mathematics
- Problem Solving

- Bilingual (English and Urdu)
- Customer Service
- Teaching
- Team Worker
- Communication

ACTIVITIES / HOBBIES

I have gained voluntary work experience at my local bakery, where I developed and deployed an electronic ordering system.

I look out for business opportunities and try to turn them into reality, as for now, I have set up my own company where I manufacture and sell textile related products worldwide.

I regularly participate in mathematic challenges and have also taken part in the National Citizen Service. For hobbies, I play club cricket as well as friendlies regularly in the summer season.

Travelling is another great hobby and passion of mine; I have travelled to numerous countries in various continents to explore different cultures.

REFERENCES

Available upon request